http://www.menopause.org.au/about-ams/privacy-statement

Contact usFeedbackHelpLinksMediaSite MapMembers Login
HomeAbout AMSAMS Executive and BoardAMS ConstitutionAMS Annual ReportsMission and VisionDocument on Conflict of InterestAccreditationHON AffiliationCode of EthicsContact usFeedbackMediaAMS in the mediaMedia KitPrivacy StatementSitemapFeaturesWhat's NewWebsite HelpMembersMembersMembers LoginMembers HelpMembership ApplicationMembership RenewalChanges MagazineIMS Menopause LiveHealth ProfessionalsAMS CongressPast Congress MeetingsConferencesHP eNewsAMS HP Videos Information SheetsInformation Sheets by Management AreaMenopause ManagementMenopause BasicsTreatment OptionsEarly MenopauseRisks and BenefitsUro-genitalBonesSex and Psychological Alternative TherapiesContraceptionMenopause - a PrimerMenopause NAMS VideosNAMS Annual Meeting 2017Cochrane ReviewsBooksEducationMenopause Essentials UpdateeDM MEUGP & HP ResourcesLinksJournalsMedical DatabasesNewsPosition StatementsStudies publishedConsumer InformationFind an AMS doctorACTNSWNTQLDSATASVICWANew ZealandBook ReviewsAMS Videos for WomenInfographicsMenopause what are the symptoms?Maintaining your weight and health during and after menopauseWhat is Menopausal Hormone Therapy (MHT) and is it safe?Maori: Menopause what are the symptoms?Maori: What is Menopausal Hormone Therapy (MHT) and is it safe?Vietnamese: Menopause what are the symptoms?Vietnamese: What is Menopausal Hormone Therapy (MHT) and is it safe?NewsResourcesFact SheetsMenopause what are the symptoms?Non-hormonal treatment options for menopausal symptomsWhat is Menopausal Hormone Therapy (MHT) and is it safe?Complementary medicine options for menopausal symptomsWill menopause affect my sex life?Bioidentical Hormone Therapy9 myths and misunderstandings about MHTLifestyle and behaviour changes for menopausal symptomsMenopause before 40 and spontaneous POIEarly menopause – chemotherapy and radiation therapyMaintaining your weight and health during and after menopauseVaginal health after breast cancer: A guide for patientsVaginal Laser TherapyDecreasing the risk of falls and fracturesUrinary Incontinence in WomenMenopause Videos for Women from NAMSMenopause Videos CantoneseMenopause Videos MandarinMenopause Videos VietnameseMenopause VideosMenopause - What are the symptomsMenopause - How will it affect my health?What is Menopausal Hormone Therapy (HRT)?Is Menopausal Hormone Therapy (HRT) safe?Menopause - Complementary TherapiesMenopause - Non-hormonal Treatment OptionsMenopause - Will it affect my sex life?Self Assessment ToolsAre you at risk of breast cancer?Are you at risk of cardiovascular disease?Are you at risk of osteoporotic fracture?Statin/Aspirin Choice Decision AidKnow your bonesKnow your chancesRisk Checker - 5 minute health questionnaireStudies RecruitingWorld Menopause Day
HomeAbout AMSPrivacy Statement
Privacy Statement
Privacy Statement for the AMS Website
The Australasian Menopause Society Limited (AMS) has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following sections disclose the information gathering and dissemination practices that are operating on our website
Collecting Information
When you visit this website, we may make a record of your visit and log some or all of the following information for statistical or maintenance purposes:
Your server or IP address (the name or number which uniquely identify the computer through which you are connected to the Internet)
The address of the referring site
The date and time of your visit
Your top level domain name (eg .org.au,gov.au etc)
The address of the pages accessed and the documents downloaded
The type of browser you used
No attempt, however, will be made to identify individual users or their browsing activities, unless required by law, nor will broad demographic information be used for marketing or general contact purposes. Your e-mail address will only be recorded if you send us a message via any of the contact forms. It will only be used for the purpose for which you have provided it and it will not be added to a mailing list, nor disclosed without your consent.
Google Analytics
Currently we are using Google Analytics to analyse the audience of the website and improve our content. No personal information is collected from Google Analytics. For further information on the privacy policy concerning Google Analytics, please go here.
Email Addresses
The AMS will record your e-mail address if you send us a message requesting us to do so for a particular purpose or activity. Your email will be used for the purpose for which you have provided it and will not be added to a mailing list unless you request us to do so. We will not use your e-mail address for any other purpose, and will not disclose it, without your consent.
Third Party Access to Information
Except where specified to the contrary, it is our policy not to sell or pass on any personal information that you may have provided to us unless we have your express consent to do so, or where we are required by law to do so.
Supplemental Information
The AMS website contains links to other sites. The AMS is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these websites.
Contacting the Website
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Website, please visit our contact page for contact information, or use the feedback form. Australasian Menopause Society Limited
Content updated November 2016
Print
Email
Find a Doctor
Find an AMS doctor with a specific interest in women's health at midlife and menopause, and the promotion of healthy ageing.
Latest News
AMS eLearning Website access
HRT and Breast Cancer Risk Position Statement
Age, education, and surgical history affect hormone use after oophorectomy
iCARE Covid-19 International Survey 4
Early Menopause: New digital resources for women and health professionals
Australian study links early menstruation to increased menopause symptoms
HP eNews
This site complies with the
HONcode standard for trustworthy health information: verify here.
© Australasian Menopause Society Limited
Information
Accreditation Contact us Disclaimer Editorial Policy FeedbackMedia Privacy StatementSite Map
Quick Links
Apply to be a MemberConferences eChanges MagazineFind an AMS DoctorIMS LiveInfographicsInformation SheetsMember eNews
AMS: ABN 69 867 357 105 | Website by Impagination
Search
HomeAbout AMSAMS Executive and BoardAMS ConstitutionAMS Annual ReportsMission and VisionDocument on Conflict of InterestAccreditationHON AffiliationCode of EthicsContact usFeedbackMediaAMS in the mediaMedia KitPrivacy StatementSitemapFeaturesWhat's NewWebsite HelpMembersMembersMembers LoginMembers HelpMembership ApplicationMembership RenewalChanges MagazineIMS Menopause LiveHealth ProfessionalsAMS CongressPast Congress MeetingsConferencesHP eNewsAMS HP Videos Information SheetsInformation Sheets by Management AreaMenopause ManagementMenopause BasicsTreatment OptionsEarly MenopauseRisks and BenefitsUro-genitalBonesSex and Psychological Alternative TherapiesContraceptionMenopause - a PrimerMenopause NAMS VideosNAMS Annual Meeting 2017Cochrane ReviewsBooksEducationMenopause Essentials UpdateeDM MEUGP & HP ResourcesLinksJournalsMedical DatabasesNewsPosition StatementsStudies publishedConsumer InformationFind an AMS doctorACTNSWNTQLDSATASVICWANew ZealandBook ReviewsAMS Videos for WomenInfographicsMenopause what are the symptoms?Maintaining your weight and health during and after menopauseWhat is Menopausal Hormone Therapy (MHT) and is it safe?Maori: Menopause what are the symptoms?Maori: What is Menopausal Hormone Therapy (MHT) and is it safe?Vietnamese: Menopause what are the symptoms?Vietnamese: What is Menopausal Hormone Therapy (MHT) and is it safe?NewsResourcesFact SheetsMenopause what are the symptoms?Non-hormonal treatment options for menopausal symptomsWhat is Menopausal Hormone Therapy (MHT) and is it safe?Complementary medicine options for menopausal symptomsWill menopause affect my sex life?Bioidentical Hormone Therapy9 myths and misunderstandings about MHTLifestyle and behaviour changes for menopausal symptomsMenopause before 40 and spontaneous POIEarly menopause – chemotherapy and radiation therapyMaintaining your weight and health during and after menopauseVaginal health after breast cancer: A guide for patientsVaginal Laser TherapyDecreasing the risk of falls and fracturesUrinary Incontinence in WomenMenopause Videos for Women from NAMSMenopause Videos CantoneseMenopause Videos MandarinMenopause Videos VietnameseMenopause VideosMenopause - What are the symptomsMenopause - How will it affect my health?What is Menopausal Hormone Therapy (HRT)?Is Menopausal Hormone Therapy (HRT) safe?Menopause - Complementary TherapiesMenopause - Non-hormonal Treatment OptionsMenopause - Will it affect my sex life?Self Assessment ToolsAre you at risk of breast cancer?Are you at risk of cardiovascular disease?Are you at risk of osteoporotic fracture?Statin/Aspirin Choice Decision AidKnow your bonesKnow your chancesRisk Checker - 5 minute health questionnaireStudies RecruitingWorld Menopause Day
